mobiletechreview.com 2019-04-17

# MobileTechReview.com Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

We do not ask for any information from you when you visit our site. WordPress may assign you a cookie so that it can improve your experience by featuring new content vs. content you've already seen, and setting language and time based on your IP address. 

We will never sell your name or any other information about you to a 3rd party.

Cookies and Other Tracking Methods

All Disqus comment system users are assigned a cookie. Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Their cookies aare used to help us make the site more usable and useful for you (for example, to keep you logged into their comment system across a variety of sites so you need not log in again each time you wish to comment). To learn more, please visit their privacy policy on their site: https://help.disqus.com/terms-and-policies/disqus-privacy-policy.

With the exception of the Disqus comment system, you will be able to use this site without any problem if you have cookies disabled or turned off.

Third Party Ad Servers

Advertising on our site originates from outside advertisers and/or advertising agencies. In some cases, if you click on or view these ads, a cookie may be assigned by the advertiser. Mobiletechreview.com does not control these cookies nor the content of the sites linked to by banner ads. Our ad-serving partners, [ZiffDavis](http://www.ziffdavistech.com/), Google and [Exponential](http://www.exponential.com/), may record cookies to prevent repetitious ad banner placement and to improve the appeal and relevance of ads.

These ad companies may use information (generally, not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this web site and to other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may employ cookies and clear GIFs to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear GIFs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message). We encourage you to read these businesses' privacy policies if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your personal information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, see the Network Advertising Initiative's consumer web site at [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

Exponential Interactive, Inc, as our partner, have a legitimate interest to collect and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website in order to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. For more details including opt-out requests, access requests or complaints, please review their [privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) or contact their data protection officer via privacy@exponential.com. 

Affiliate Links, Shopping Links

Note: mobiletechreview.com places links on our site to purchase merchandise from outside vendors such as [Amazon.com](http://www.amazon.com/). These are our ecommerce affiliates. In some cases, if you click on a link to buy merchandise, a cookie may be assigned by the vendor or by the firms that manages other affiliate network relationships. Mobiletechreview.com does not control these cookies. 

Links

The mobiletechreview.com site contains links to other Web sites. Mobiletechreview.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Please read the privacy policies of those Web sites you choose to visit.

Your Consent

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of the information as outlined within this privacy policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

Contact Information:  [webmaster@mobiletechreview.com](mailto:webmaster@mobiletechreview.com)
